Fred Crawford Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Lowell Thomas Papers Research File, 6; Boxes: 52 - 169
  - Carr, Ralph, 1939 - 1950 (Folder 13, Box 70)
  - Cars, 1930 - 1955 (Folder 14, Box 70)
  - Cars: Accidents + Insurance, 1932 - 1954 (Folder 15, Box 70)
  - Carson, Ralph, 1941 - 1977 (Folder 16, Box 70)
  - Carter, Boake (10th), 1940 - 1949 (Folder 17, Box 70)
  - Carter, Jas. Earl, 1976 - 1979 (Folder 18, Box 70)
  - Cartoon Digest (Advisory Board), 1939 (Folder 19, Box 70)
  - Case, Nelson, 1955 - 1976 (Folder 20, Box 70)
  - Casey, WM, 1954 November 26 (Folder 21, Box 70)
  - Caual Code of Europe (Hurd), 1958 - 1959 (Folder 22, Box 70)
  - CBS, 1932 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 71)
  - CBS + LTJ (Lowell Thomas Jr.), 1954 - 1960 (Folder 2, Box 71)
  - CBS 1967 Letters, 1950 - 1967 (Folder 3, Box 71)
  - CBS Botch, 1974 - 1977 (Folder 4, Box 71)
  - CBS 1967 Contract, 1967 - 1977 (Folder 5, Box 71)
  - CBS Employees, 1954 (Folder 6, Box 71)
  - CBS/HOM, 1966 (Folder 7, Box 71)
  - CBS Lines, 1946 - 1969 (Folder 8, Box 71)
  - CBS News Policy, 1947 (Folder 9, Box 71)
  - CBS Stations, 1954 (Folder 10, Box 71)
  - Censorship, 1935 - 1946 (Folder 11, Box 71)
  - Chain Letter, 1941 (Folder 12, Box 71)
  - Chain System, 1940 - 1942 (Folder 13, Box 71)
  - Chamberlain, Frank, 1932 - 1938 (Folder 14, Box 71)
  - Chamberlain, Paul, 1915 (Folder 15, Box 71)
  - Chamberlain, Frank, 1978 (Folder 16, Box 71)
  - Chamberlain, Rene De, 1940 - 1969 (Folder 17, Box 71)
  - Chaplain Miller Appeal, 1946 (Folder 18, Box 71)
  - Charmonz, 1938 - 1981 (Folder 19, Box 71)
  - Chart, 1939 July 8 (Folder 20, Box 71)
  - Chase, Dean, 1940 - 1948 (Folder 21, Box 71)
  - Chennault, 1949 (Folder 22, Box 71)
  - Chess, 1981 (Folder 23, Box 71)
  - Cheualier, John B. " Chevy ", 1946 - 1952 (Folder 24, Box 71)
  - 1, 1966 (Folder 1, Box 72)
  - 2, 1917 - 1981 (Folder 2, Box 72)
  - 3, 1925 (Folder 3, Box 72)
  - 4, 1916 - 1943 (Folder 4, Box 72)
  - 5, 1914 - 1981 (Folder 5, Box 72)
  - 6, 1948 - 1977 (Folder 6, Box 72)
  - 7, 1935 - 1937 (Folder 7, Box 72)
  - 8, 1941 - 1963 (Folder 8, Box 72)
  - 9, 1934 (Folder 9, Box 72)
  - 10, 1946 - 1977 (Folder 10, Box 72)
  - 11, 1935 - 1981 (Folder 11, Box 72)
  - 12, 1960 - (Folder 12, Box 72)
  - 13, 1947 - 1963 (Folder 13, Box 72)
  - 14, 1963 - 1964 (Folder 14, Box 72)
  - 15, 1964 - 1967 (Folder 15, Box 72)
  - 16, 1967 - 1976 (Folder 16, Box 72)
  - Christl Book, 1963 - 1976 (Folder 1, Box 73)
  - Christmas Card (signed), undated (Folder 2, Box 73)
  - Christmas, 1942 - 1952 (Folder 3, Box 73)
  - Christmas Lists, 1940 - 1949 (Folder 4, Box 73)
  - Christophery (Tel Groupie), 1941 (Folder 5, Box 73)
  - Chronology, 1892 - 1981 (Folder 6, Box 73)
  - Chrysler Promo, 1924 (Folder 7, Box 73)
  - Churchill, 1941 - 1965 (Folder 8, Box 73)
  - CIA, 1941 - 1981 (Folder 9, Box 73)
  - Cigars, 1950 (Folder 10, Box 73)
  - Cinelog, 1933 (Folder 11, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [1 of 4], 1950 - 1951 (Folder 12, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [2 of 4], 1951 - 1952 (Folder 13, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [3 of 4], 1952 - 1953 (Folder 14, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [4 of 4], 1953 (Folder 15, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [1 of 6], 1953 April -June (Folder 16, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [2 of 6], 1953 June - August (Folder 17, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [3 of 6], 1953 September - November (Folder 18, Box 73)
  - Cinerama [4 of 6], 1953 November - 1954 September (Folder 1, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [5 of 6], 1954 September - 1955 February (Folder 2, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [6 of 6], 1955 February - December (Folder 3, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [1 of 5], 1956 (Folder 4, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [2 of 5], 1956 - 1959 (Folder 5, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [3 of 5], 1959 - 1962 (Folder 6, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [4 of 5], 1962 - 1973 (Folder 7, Box 74)
  - Cinerama [5 of 5], 1973 - 1980 (Folder 8, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Acheson Memo, 1953 (Folder 9, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Cinerama and Hi Ad [High Adventure], 1958 (Folder 10, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Arkell, 1952 - 1965 (Folder 11, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Ataullah, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 12, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Boeing, 1958 (Folder 13, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Boris, 1957 (Folder 14, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Braley, 1956 (Folder 15, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Brit Crit, 1958 (Folder 16, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Brussels Fair, 1958 (Folder 17, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Cinemiracle, 1957 (Folder 18, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - (Cine) - Rama, 1957 - 1958 (Folder 19, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Cinimage, 1973 (Folder 20, Box 74)
  - Cinerama - Coop, 1943 - 1972 (Folder 1, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Cinerama/Coop, 1979 (Folder 2, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Customs, 1957 (Folder 3, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Damascus Fair, 1954 (Folder 4, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Datable?, undated (Folder 5, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Dulles, 1954 - 1958 (Folder 6, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Dyrenfurth, 1953 (Folder 7, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Amer [American], 1953 July - September (Folder 8, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Essay Contest, 1953 (Folder 9, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Farnol, 1959 - 1963 (Folder 10, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Flaherty, 1941 - 1951 (Folder 11, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Foreign, 1957 (Folder 12, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Holiday Openings, 1955 (Folder 13, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Cinike (Cinerama), 1952 - 1956 (Folder 14, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Ideas, 1953 - 1959 (Folder 15, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - India, 1956 - 1958 (Folder 16, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Japan, 1953 (Folder 17, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Lang, 1952 - 1972 (Folder 18, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Larrinaga, 1955 - 1972 (Folder 19, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Liddell Hart, 1955 (Folder 20, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Lipscomb, 1953 - 1958 (Folder 21, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Mayer, 1952 (Folder 22, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - MD, 1955 (Folder 23, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Morrison, 1955 (Folder 24, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Legal, ETC, 1951 - 1956 (Folder 25, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - PAL, 1975 (Folder 26, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Parker, 1956 (Folder 27, Box 75)
  - Cinerama - Plaque, 1957 - 1960 (Folder 1, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Reeves, 1935 - 1938 (Folder 2, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Reisini, 1959 - 1963 (Folder 3, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Programs, 1952 - 1958 (Folder 4, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Remote, 1954 - 1956 (Folder 5, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Russhoon, 1952 (Folder 6, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Saints and Sinners, 1961? (Folder 7, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Accident, 1956 - 1960 (Folder 8, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search Artwork, 1956 (Folder 9, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search (Blitz), 1956 (Folder 10, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search Book, 1957 (Folder 11, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Breakdown Reels, 1956 (Folder 12, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search Credits, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 13, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search -Ethics, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 14, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Gov't [Government], 1956 - 1958 (Folder 15, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Gov't [Government] (Vaccine), 1956 (Folder 16, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search -Hunza, 1948 - 1967 (Folder 17, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search Music, 1957 (Folder 18, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search Openings, 1957 - 1958 (Folder 19, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Lang, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 20, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Legal, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 21, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search - Personnel, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 22, Box 76)
  - Cinerama - Search Reitzel, Bok, 1956 (Folder 1, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Search - Remote CBS, 1956 (Folder 2, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Search Reviews, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 3, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Search Rockefeller Laurane, 1959 - 1960 (Folder 4, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Final Script Continuity " Search for Paradise ", undated (Folder 5, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Search - Sewall, Barbara Jean, 1956 - 1966 (Folder 6, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Search Summation (LT [Lowell Thomas]), 1972 (Folder 7, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Search - Tiomkin, 1956 - 1981 (Folder 8, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Apprec [Appreciation], 1955 - 1957 (Folder 9, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Book, 1955 - 1974 (Folder 10, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Corr [Correction], 1957 (Folder 11, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Credits, 1955 - 1957 (Folder 12, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Critics/ + Aihamkler, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 13, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Legal, 1954 - 1956 (Folder 14, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Mantz Schedule, 1954 (Folder 15, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Mantz, 1954 - 1955 (Folder 16, Box 77)
  - Cinerama -] 7W [Seven Wonders] Mats, 1955 (Folder 17, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] New Term, 1956? (Folder 18, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Winchell, 1952 (Folder 19, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Tuir, 1956 (Folder 20, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Truman, 1953 (Folder 21, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Todd, 1951 - 1966 (Folder 22, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - Ticket Flaps, 1953 - 1960 (Folder 23, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Outline, 1954 (Folder 24, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Pan Am, 1954 - 1955 (Folder 25, Box 77)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Personnel (Field), 1955 (Folder 1, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Personnel (Theatre), 1957 (Folder 2, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Pub [Publications] + Reviews, 1956 - 1960 (Folder 3, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Remote, 1953 (Folder 4, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Req, 1972 (Folder 5, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] " Shooting the Pope ", 1954 (Folder 6, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - Syracuse, 1958 (Folder 7, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Tech, 1958 (Folder 8, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - Smith, 1950 - 1954 (Folder 9, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - Summary (LT [Lowell Thomas]), 1954 November (Folder 10, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Open, 1956 - 1957 (Folder 11, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Churchill + Murrow, 1954 - 1955 (Folder 12, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Gov't [Government], 1952 - 1958 (Folder 13, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Pub [Publicity] + Review, 1956 - 1960 (Folder 14, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - 7W [Seven Wonders] Odds +Ends, 1954? (Folder 15, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - Cinerama Technology, 1950 - 1957 (Folder 16, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] Cooper Flap, 1953 (Folder 17, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] Credits, undated (Folder 18, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] Critics (Texas), 1953 (Folder 19, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - This, 1951 - 1956 (Folder 20, Box 78)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] - Personnel, 1953 (Folder 1, Box 79)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] - Plugs-Peale, 1952 (Folder 2, Box 79)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] Reviews + Pub [Publications], 1951 - 1954 (Folder 3, Box 79)
  - Cinerama - This Tech, 1953 (Folder 4, Box 79)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] Openings, undated (Folder 5, Box 79)
  - Cinerama - This [is Cinerama] Tickets, Apprec [Appreciation], Extracts, 1952 - 1957 (Folder 6, Box 79)
  - Circumnavigators, 1934 - 1981 (Folder 7, Box 79)
  - Circus S+S, 1931 - 1974 (Folder 8, Box 79)
  - Clark, High, 1942 - 1944 (Folder 9, Box 79)
  - Clark, J. Ruben, 1955 - 1961 (Folder 10, Box 79)
  - Clark, Mark, 1945 - 1979 (Folder 11, Box 79)
  - Clark, Neil M., 1966 (Folder 12, Box 79)
  - Clark, Pat, 1936 - 1959 (Folder 13, Box 79)
  - Clark, Pat - Movietones, 1935 (Folder 14, Box 79)
  - Clark Place, 1942 (Folder 15, Box 79)
  - Clear, Frank, 1938 - 1943 (Folder 16, Box 79)
  - Class, 1944 (Folder 17, Box 79)
  - Clips, 1969 - 1973 (Folder 18, Box 79)
  - Clock, 1933 - 1938 (Folder 19, Box 79)
  - Close, Upton, 1935 - 1941 (Folder 20, Box 79)
  - Clothes, 1936 - 1976 (Folder 21, Box 79)
  - Clover Brook, 1926 - 1977 (Folder 22, Box 79)
  - Clover Brook Barn, 1940 (Folder 23, Box 79)
  - Cochran, Bob, 1952 (Folder 24, Box 79)
  - Cochran, Phil/Tom, 1975 - 1979 (Folder 25, Box 79)
  - Cog [Train], 1972 - 1976 (Folder 26, Box 79)
  - Cold, 1937 - 1947 (Folder 27, Box 79)
  - Cole, Ed, 1971 - 1977 (Folder 28, Box 79)
  - Colex Weber Commercial, 1980 (Folder 29, Box 79)
  - Colgate Show, 1941 (Folder 30, Box 79)
  - Collieris, 1940 - 1956 (Folder 31, Box 79)
  - Collings, 1938 - 1964 (Folder 32, Box 79)
  - Collingwood, 1949 - 1978 (Folder 33, Box 79)
  - Collins, D. Stone, 1963 (Folder 34, Box 79)
  - Collins, E.D., 1939 - 1967 (Folder 35, Box 79)
  - Colo [Colorado] Ranch (Tiffany), 1931 - 1946 (Folder 36, Box 79)
  - Colorado Olympics, 1966 (Folder 37, Box 79)
  - Comfort, Mildred, 1962 - 1980 (Folder 38, Box 79)
  - Commentator, 1936 - 1949 (Folder 1, Box 80)
  - Commercial, 1936 - 1968 (Folder 2, Box 80)
  - Comp, 1939 - 1950 (Folder 3, Box 80)
  - Compton (Advertising), 1946 - 1955 (Folder 4, Box 80)
  - Comstock, Ruth, 1976 - 1978 (Folder 5, Box 80)
  - " Confused " Figures, 1948 (Folder 6, Box 80)
  - Conklin, Geo, W., 1951 (Folder 7, Box 80)
  - Connellan, 1958 - 1980 (Folder 8, Box 80)
  - Considine, 1948 - 1963 (Folder 9, Box 80)
  - Constant (Ski), 1945 - 1946 (Folder 10, Box 80)
  - Contest Judge, 1931 - 1940 (Folder 11, Box 80)
  - Convention, 1932 (Folder 12, Box 80)
  - Conventions, 1936 (Folder 13, Box 80)
  - Convention, 1940 (Folder 14, Box 80)
  - Conventions, 1944 (Folder 15, Box 80)
  - Conventions, 1948 (Folder 16, Box 80)
  - Convention, 1952 (Folder 17, Box 80)
  - Convention, 1956 (Folder 18, Box 80)
  - Convention, 1960 (Folder 19, Box 80)
  - Convention, 1972 (Folder 20, Box 80)
  - Conventions, 1980 (Folder 21, Box 80)
  - Cook, Frederick, 1965 - 1973 (Folder 22, Box 80)
  - Cook, John V., 1967 - 1971 (Folder 23, Box 80)
  - Coolidge, Caluin, 1938 (Folder 24, Box 80)
  - Cooper, Edwin, 1939 - 1942 (Folder 25, Box 80)
  - Cooper, Merian, 1932 - 1973 (Folder 26, Box 80)
  - Coop - Space, 1962 (Folder 1936 - 1949, Box 81)
  - Cooper, Pherbia, 1938 - 1981 (Folder 1936 - 1968, Box 81)
  - Coppock, 1960 - 1972 (Folder 1939 - 1950, Box 81)
  - Corn Liquor, 1978 (Folder 1946 - 1955, Box 81)
  - Coronation, 1937 (Folder 1976 - 1978, Box 81)
  - Coronation, 1953 (Folder 1948, Box 81)
  - Coronation, 1957 (Folder 1951, Box 81)
  - Corrections, 1931 - 1975 (Folder 1958 - 1980, Box 81)
  - " Corrections ", 1943 - 1960 (Folder 1948 - 1963, Box 81)
  - Corrections - Fact, 1942 - 1949 (Folder 1945 - 1946, Box 81)
  - " Corrections " - Religious, 1947 - 1957 (Folder 1931 - 1940, Box 81)
  - Corrigan, 1938 (Folder 1932, Box 81)
  - Corsets, 1942 (Folder 1936, Box 81)
  - Cotlow, Lewis, 1966 (Folder 1940, Box 81)
  - Cotton, 1931 (Folder 1944, Box 81)
  - Coughlin, 1935 - 1940 (Folder 1948, Box 81)
  - Court of Last Resort, 1949 - 1950 (Folder 1952, Box 81)
  - Courtenay, WM, 1938 - 1960 (Folder 1956, Box 81)
  - Courtship, 1915 - 1916 (Folder 1960, Box 81)
  - Cousins, Bob, 1955 - 1959 (Folder 1972, Box 81)
  - Cowan, Geo. E., Jr., 1933 - 1941 (Folder 1980, Box 81)
  - Cowling, Herford Tynes, 1929 - 1946 (Folder 1965 - 1973, Box 81)
  - Cowling, WWI Film, 1932 (Folder 1967 - 1971, Box 81)
  - Cragston Club, 1932 (Folder 1938, Box 81)
  - Crawford, F.C., 1956 - 1976 (Folder 1939 - 1942, Box 81)
  - Crawford, Bob, 1932 - 1961 (Folder 1932 - 1973, Box 81)
  - Creel, George, 1931 - 1947 (Folder 1, Box 82)
  - Cripple Creek, 1918 - 1981 (Folder 2, Box 82)
  - Cripple Creek Last Train, 1949 (Folder 3, Box 82)
  - Crissey, Paul, 1972 - 1976 (Folder 4, Box 82)
  - Critics [1 of 4], 1931 - 1941 (Folder 5, Box 82)
  - Critics [2 of 4], 1941 - 1947 (Folder 6, Box 82)
  - Critics [3 of 4], 1947 - 1956 (Folder 7, Box 82)
  - Critics [4 of 4], 1956 - 1972 (Folder 8, Box 82)
  - Critic - Announcer, 1953 (Folder 9, Box 82)
  - Critic (Cartoon), 1939 January 20 (Folder 10, Box 82)
  - Critic - Coolidge, 1938 (Folder 11, Box 82)
  - Critic Crank, 1956 (Folder 12, Box 82)
  - Critic - Endorse, 1943 (Folder 13, Box 82)
  - Critic - Form Responses, 1943 (Folder 14, Box 82)
  - Critic - Radical, 1941 - 1951 (Folder 15, Box 82)
  - Critic - Religion, 1934 - 1961 (Folder 16, Box 82)
  - Critic -U.S.S.R, 1945 - 1957 (Folder 17, Box 82)
  - Critic - [Female?], 1935 (Folder 18, Box 82)
  - Cronkhite Walker, 1939 (Folder 19, Box 82)
  - Cronkite, 1960 - 1981 (Folder 20, Box 82)
  - Crosby, Bing, 1977 (Folder 21, Box 82)
  - Crosley Radio, 1935 - 1942 (Folder 1, Box 83)
  - Crouse/Miller, 1959 - 1965 (?) (Folder 2, Box 83)
  - Crowe Flap, 1931 (Folder 3, Box 83)
  - Crowell - Collier, 1939 - 1952 (Folder 4, Box 83)
  - Croy, 1934 - 1966 (Folder 5, Box 83)
  - Cruise (1929), 1929 - 1981 (Folder 6, Box 83)
  - Cruise?, 1976 (Folder 7, Box 83)
  - Cruise Promo (Brilez [?]), 1975 (Folder 8, Box 83)
  - Cubbedge, Robert, 1964 - 1981 (Folder 9, Box 83)
  - Cuddihy, 1952 - 1953 (Folder 10, Box 83)
  - Curtiss, Bill, 1960 (Folder 11, Box 83)
  - Customs LTR, 1955 (Folder 12, Box 83)
  - " Cute ", 1951 (Folder 13, Box 83)
  - D - Day, 1944 (Folder 14, Box 83)
  - DHL Inquiry, 1980 (Folder 15, Box 83)
  - Daily Telegraph, 1935 - 1936 (Folder 16, Box 83)
  - Dalai Lama, 1961 - 1979 (Folder 17, Box 83)
  - Dale House, 1951 (Folder 18, Box 83)
  - Dance, 1936 - 1937 (Folder 19, Box 83)
  - Daniels, Ross (insurance), 1935, 1966 - 1981 (Folder 20, Box 83)
  - Dargue, 1935 - 1977 (Folder 21, Box 83)
  - Darrow, 1913 - 1932 (Folder 22, Box 83)
  - Dartmouth, 1947 - 1978 (Folder 23, Box 83)
  - Dartmouth - Hopkins, 1948 (Folder 24, Box 83)
  - Dauis, Mary, 1937 - 1966 (Folder 25, Box 83)
  - Dauis, Mary, to John Lerchon H.A. [High Adventure], 1964 (Folder 26, Box 83)
  - Dauis - Endorse, 1940 (Folder 27, Box 83)
  - Lit D Dauis, Mary, 1931 (Folder 28, Box 83)
  - Davis, Col. [Colonel] Edw. [Edward] (Tei [?]), 1942 - 1953 (Folder 29, Box 83)
  - Davis, Elmer, 1944 (Folder 30, Box 83)
  - Dawson, A.K. (AMX), 1934 (Folder 1, Box 84)
  - Daylight Savings Time, 1938 (Folder 2, Box 84)
  - Daylogue, 1919 - 1924 (Folder 3, Box 84)
  - Dayton, 1934 April 18 (Folder 4, Box 84)
  - Dean, Faye, 1975 (Folder 5, Box 84)
  - Dean, Jimmy, 1981 July 3 (Folder 6, Box 84)
  - (Dizzy) Dean Botch, 1938 (Folder 7, Box 84)
  - Death Ray, 1940 (Folder 8, Box 84)
  - Debo, 1975 - 1978 (Folder 9, Box 84)
  - Debts (Old), 1928 - 1942 (Folder 10, Box 84)
  - Delco, 1958 July 9 (Folder 11, Box 84)
  - Dempsey, 1965 - 1975 (Folder 12, Box 84)
  - Denious, Wilbur F. (UD), undated (Folder 13, Box 84)
  - Dentist, 1934 - 1966 (Folder 14, Box 84)
  - Denver Newsdays, 1912 (Folder 15, Box 84)
  - Denver Olympics, 1972 (Folder 16, Box 84)
  - University of Denver [1 of 3], 1932 - 1970 (Folder 17, Box 84)
  - University of Denver [2 of 3], 1970 - 1978 (Folder 18, Box 84)
  - University of Denver [3 of 3], 1978 - 1981 (Folder 19, Box 84)
  - Denver U [University] Days - M.A., 1913 (Folder 20, Box 84)
  - Denver U [University] Days, 1913 - 1962 (Folder 21, Box 84)
  - Denver U [University] Days - Mcfarlane, 1940 (Folder 1, Box 85)
  - Denya, Marcelle [Mrs. Philip Courtney], 1943? (Folder 2, Box 85)
  - Dept [Department] of Defense (Lairo), 1973 (Folder 3, Box 85)
  - Dept [Department] of State, 1937 - 1956 (Folder 4, Box 85)
  - Dewey [LTR for the Taxabuses], 1948 July 7 (Folder 5, Box 85)
  - Detroit Hospital, 1963 November (Folder 6, Box 85)
  - Devlin, 1942 - 1949 (Folder 7, Box 85)
  - Dewey [1 of 2], 1937 - 1944 (Folder 8, Box 85)
  - Dewey [2 of 2], 1944 - 1980 (Folder 9, Box 85)
  - Dewey Film, 1948? (Folder 10, Box 85)
  - Dewey/FDR Radio Flak [?], 1944 (Folder 11, Box 85)
  - Diary (Norton, FRT), 1915 (Folder 12, Box 85)
  - Diary - Cont'd [Continued], 1915 (Folder 13, Box 85)
  - Diary, 1938 (Folder 1, Box 86)
  - Dickler, 1952 - 1981 (Folder 2, Box 86)
  - Dictionary Flap, 1931 (Folder 3, Box 86)
  - Dies Committee, 1938 - 1940 (Folder 4, Box 86)
  - Dinner - Storrst, 1939 January 11 (Folder 5, Box 86)
  - Dionne Quints, 1935 - 1946 (Folder 6, Box 86)
  - Discouragement (FRT), 1923 (Folder 7, Box 86)
  - Disney, 1938 - 1960 (Folder 8, Box 86)
  - Disney World, 1981 (Folder 9, Box 86)
  - Divorce, 1978 (Folder 10, Box 86)
  - Doctorate (Albright), 1935 (Folder 11, Box 86)
  - Dogs, 1934 - 1979 (Folder 12, Box 86)
  - Dole, Minne, 1964 - 1974 (Folder 13, Box 86)
  - Don Lee Mutual, 1940 - 1944 (Folder 14, Box 86)
  - Dooley, 1972 March 29 (Folder 15, Box 86)
  - Doolittle, Jimmy, 1929 - 1981 (Folder 16, Box 86)
  - Doolittle Book, 1933 - 1978 (Folder 17, Box 86)
  - Doolittle Book + Hoyt, 1970 - 1978 (Folder 18, Box 86)
  - Double Entendres, 1950 June 2 (Folder 19, Box 86)
  - Doubleday, 1930 - 1980 (Folder 1, Box 87)
  - Doubleday Biography of FDR, 1953 (Folder 2, Box 87)
  - Doubleday Six, 1932 - 1935 (Folder 3, Box 87)
  - Dougan/Duncan, 1968 (Folder 4, Box 87)
  - Douglas, 1957 - 1981 (Folder 5, Box 87)
  - Down the Road, 1960 (Folder 6, Box 87)
  - Draper, Paul, 1940 - 1944 (Folder 7, Box 87)
  - Dray (Allen + Edna), 1967 (Folder 8, Box 87)
  - Dream Dress, 1943 December 1 (Folder 9, Box 87)
  - Drinkwater, John, 1932 (Folder 10, Box 87)
  - Drozd, 1975 - 1980 (Folder 11, Box 87)
  - Drozd Letter, 1978 November 15 (Folder 12, Box 87)
  - Drummond, 1940 July 23 (Folder 13, Box 87)
  - Dudley, Carl, 1963 - 1966 (Folder 14, Box 87)
  - Dues (Arna), 1949 (Folder 15, Box 87)
  - Dugmore, 1931 - 1955 (Folder 16, Box 87)
  - Dulles, Allan, 1955 - 1968 (Folder 17, Box 87)
  - Dulles, J.F., 1953 (Folder 18, Box 87)
  - Duncan/Ladakh, 1979 (Folder 19, Box 87)
  - Dupont Award, 1948 (Folder 20, Box 87)
  - Durlacher, 1937 - 1940 (Folder 21, Box 87)
  - Dutch Treat Club [1 of 2], 1934 - 1964 (Folder 22, Box 87)
  - Dutch Treat Club [2 of 2], 1964 - 1981 (Folder 23, Box 87)
  - Dutchess County, 1937 - 1975 (Folder 24, Box 87)
  - Dutchess (Dep Sher), 1931 - 1960 (Folder 25, Box 87)
  - Dyrenfurth, 1932 - 1980 (Folder 26, Box 87)
  - Eagan, 1941 - 1968 (Folder 1, Box 88)
  - Earhart, 1932 - 1979 (Folder 2, Box 88)
  - Early Radio, 1934 - 1976 (Folder 3, Box 88)
  - Early Writings - Denver, 1912 - 1913 (Folder 4, Box 88)
  - Eastland, 1915 (Folder 5, Box 88)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1940 - 1977 (Folder 6, Box 88)
  - Edwards, Doug, 1973 (Folder 7, Box 88)
  - Edwards, Ralph, 1961 - 1962 (Folder 8, Box 88)
  - Eichmann Trial, 1961 - 1965 (Folder 9, Box 88)
  - Edwards, Dan, 1929 - 1978 (Folder 10, Box 88)
  - Eightieth Year, 1972 (Folder 11, Box 88)
  - Eisenhower, 1948 - 1978 (Folder 12, Box 88)
  - Election Bets, 1940 - 1944 (Folder 13, Box 88)
  - Election Guide, 1936 (Folder 14, Box 88)
  - Electricity, 1947 (Folder 15, Box 88)
  - Elizabeth II, 1947 (Folder 16, Box 88)
  - Elkins, Frank, 1940 - 1974 (Folder 17, Box 88)
  - Elliot, Larry, 1973 - 1981 (Folder 18, Box 88)
  - Ellis, Kumpton, 1944 (Folder 19, Box 88)
  - Ellis, Lovel S., 1960 (Folder 20, Box 88)
  - Embezzler, 1974 (Folder 21, Box 88)
  - Gertrude Emerson Sen, 1933 - 1981 (Folder 22, Box 88)
  - Employees, 1930 - 1980 (Folder 23, Box 88)
  - Employees (Steno), 1948 - 1950 (Folder 24, Box 88)
  - Endorsements (LT [Lowell Thomas]), 1931 - 1979 (Folder 1, Box 89)
  - Endorsements Deal (LT [Lowell Thomas]), 1934 - 1945 (Folder 2, Box 89)
  - Endorsements (LT [Lowell Thomas]) Flaps, 1934 - 1957 (Folder 3, Box 89)
  - Endorsements Flap - Cancer, 1950 (Folder 4, Box 89)
  - Endorsements Flap - Midwest Radio, 1935 - 1936 (Folder 5, Box 89)
  - Endorsements Flap - Tires, 1937 (Folder 6, Box 89)
  - Endorsements - No Deal, 1931 (Folder 7, Box 89)
  - Endorsements - Whiskers, 1953 (Folder 8, Box 89)
  - Engen, 1960 March 9 (Folder 9, Box 89)
  - Engler, Max, 1947 November 29 (Folder 10, Box 89)
  - English - Speaking Union, 1945 - 1949 (Folder 11, Box 89)
  - Enloe, 1960 - 1970 (Folder 12, Box 89)
  - Ensign (Taxes), 1934 - 1942 (Folder 13, Box 89)
  - EPI [Educational Productions Inc.], 1975 - 1981 (Folder 14, Box 89)
  - Equipment, 1940 - 1967 (Folder 15, Box 89)
  - Equitable Show " T.R. ", 1960 (Folder 16, Box 89)
  - Ethics, 1935 - 1973 (Folder 17, Box 89)
  - Eunice's Diary, 1922 (Folder 18, Box 89)
  - In Europe, 1917 (Folder 19, Box 89)
  - European Credentials, 1917 - 1919 (Folder 20, Box 89)
  - European Skyways, 1926 - 1959 (Folder 21, Box 89)
  - Evans, Richard L., 1971 (Folder 22, Box 89)
  - Evans, Robt. [Robert], 1943 (Folder 23, Box 89)